What's up guys?  Brezy here and it's been a
while since we've
posted videos when it comes
to products.  So I'm going to introduce you to
one of the spider
[Music]
concepts.  So this is the spy.  So what is a
spy?  Usually, this spy is the
spider's race technology.  So here,
the race concepts or
the carbon fiber, fiber glass,
unique designs and the latest
technologies of Spider are applied to spy helmets.  So
Spider sent us one of
their new helmets.  Let's unbox
[Music]
.  As always, spiders don't
skimp.
There is a free
visor.  The helmet
bag is nice.  So what I'm going to show you about the
helmet is one of the carbon fiber
designs.  Wow.
[Music]
There's
another bomb.
Wow.  So they've noticed that
we often go on trails,
we often go offroad, and one of the things
they've noticed is my passion for super
moto, as you know.  So Spider sent us
one of their unique helmets
and this is what is called a dual
sport helmet.
So if you notice,
his helmet shell is forge composite.  That's
not ordinary carbon fiber
material.  He is forged carbon.  This means
the ones that look like they were sprinkled with carbon and
then resin was applied.  So
his design is truly unique.  The next thing we noticed here is
that on the top of the helmet, he has a
camera mount.  So go for an adventure, this is it
.  For those of you who vlog, if
you want to see or capture footage of what
you're doing, he has a
mount ready.
Beauty.  Also, I didn't mention to you,
the name of this helmet is the spider
drift.  Why is
this helmet called drift?  Because from what I see
, wherever you go, this
helmet is a go
helmet.  How beautiful.  So the gift helmet,
if we notice here,
has a
dual visor technique,
meaning it has a sun visor
inside, which is
nice.  So I did some research about
this helmet and it could
be a full face helmet.  Let me show
you.  The first thing we'll do is
take off the top.
You don't need any special tools,
even your nails will
do.  So like I said earlier,
the action camera mount is removable.
Then I said, "Can it be a
full face helmet?"  I'll show
you this.  It's simple, just unscrew
him
[Music]
here.  So the adventure helmet we saw earlier is
now a full face helmet.
This drift helmet is that beautiful
on
Spider.  So I told you earlier that a
dual sport helmet means it can
be an adventure helmet, it can be a
sport helmet.  Beauty.
Let's measure it, there's a free manual
and stickers inside the helmet.  Let's eat
this.
And this helmet, we can notice that
it doesn't have a double deering lock
mechanism.  This is the quick release.  So
if we notice here, he has an
emergency full.  Almost all spider
helmets have this feature so that in
case of emergency,
the helmet can be easily removed.   Let
's take it.  The
fittings are nice.  So almost all
spike concepts have better
inner foam, better
ventilation, but they are a bit
pricey.  So this is one of
our new helmets today and this is the
spy drift by spider.  So soon
you'll see me using this in
our future vlogs, especially in
adventures.  So this is the Spider Drip
by Spider.  So for all the time we've been
riding motorcycles, we've only trusted one helmet brand
for
our adventures.  And not only that,
I can just share it with
you.  Spider doesn't just have a helmet because
he also has a riding jacket.   There are
many varieties or choices.  There's still
street, adventure.  We also have something for
enduro.  So this is what I'm showing
you.  This is one of the
most affordable spider jackets.  Fully
padded, elbows, shoulders, back,
then mesh type, the jacket is breedable.
So you'll feel really comfortable
on the trip.  So these are some of the spider
products available on the market today.
So hopefully soon I will be able to show
you other latest riding
products.  So this is something you will always
remember.  Just stay cool.  always here.
[Music]